Guide to Records Concerning Real Property and Legal Transactions near Cripple Creek, Colorado
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Records of Identified Abstract Companies, 1871-circa 1940; Series I; 21.7; (72 boxes)
  - El Paso County Abstract Company, circa 1895-1900
    - Index to Mines, Volume C, circa 1895-1900 (Box 40 Oversize)
      Alphabetical index to mines with references to the entries to legal instruments
  - El Paso County Abstract and Title Guaranty Company, 1893-1918
    This series is arranged under three headings: Indices, Sale Records for Delinquent Taxes in Fremont and Teller Counties, and Real Estate Maps.
    El Paso County Abstract and Title Guaranty Company was an abstract company active in Cripple Creek, Colorado, circa 1890-circa 1920.
    - Indices, 1904-1918
      - Abstract Order and Delivery, Book No. 4, Entries 3922-14731, 1904 May 2-1918 December 3 (Box 41 Oversize)
      - Index to Lands, Book No. 1, undated (Box 42 Oversize)
        Index to lands in Ranges 60-68. Arranged by range, township, and section.
      - Index to Miscellaneous Towns and Additions, undated (Box 43 Oversize)
        Compiles two discrete volumes that index property lots in towns, additions, and subdivisions. Settlements include Arensdale, Calvert Heights, Colorado City, Colorado Springs, Florissant, Fountain, Glen Park, Granger, Montclair, and Palmer Lake.
    - Sale Records for Delinquent Taxes in Fremont and Teller Counties, 1893-1901
      Records of sales of real estate for delinquent taxes in Fremont and Teller Counties.
      - Tax Sale Record, Fremont County, Entries 1881-3503 and 1-4142, 1893 December 3-1900 December 7 (Box 44 Oversize)
        First portion documents the sale in Fremont County from December 3, 1893, to December 13, 1898, and certificate entries 1881-3503, for properties that later became part of Teller County.
        Second portion documents the sale on December 8, 1899, with certificate entries 1-1420.
        Third portion documents the sale December 6-7, 1900, with certificate entries 1421-4142.
      - Tax Sale Record, Teller County, No. 3, Entries 4143-7261, 1901 November 19-20 (Box 45 Oversize)
    - Real Estate Maps, circa 1900
      Volumes of maps that document real estate in Colorado Springs and the Cripple Creek Region of Colorado.
      - Plat Book No. 1, circa 1900 (Box 46 Oversize)
        Bound volume with manuscript plat maps for Colorado Springs, Colorado.
        Maps chiefly identify plats in Township 14 South, Ranges 66-67 West; as well as Township 13 South Range 66 West; Township 11 South, Ranges 67 and 69 West; Township 16 West, Range 65 West; and Township 12 South, Range 69 West.
      - Township Diagram Book, circa 1900 (Box 47 Oversize)
        Volume with township diagrams for townships, usually 11-17, in Ranges 60-71 West. Diagrams include notes that probably refer to property records.
  - Fremont Abstract Company, 1891-1897
    Fremont Abstract Company was an abstract company active in Cañon City, Colorado, circa 1890-circa 1900.
    - Lots, Fremont, 1891-1897 (Box 48 Oversize)
      Volume records entry numbers for property lots in Fremont, Colorado, and its additions.
  - Security Abstract & Title Company, 1901-1935
    This series is arranged under two headings: Abstracts of Legal Instruments in El Paso County by Date and Records of a Notary Public.
    Security Abstract & Title Company was an abstract company active in Colorado Springs, Colorado, circa 1900-circa 1940.
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments in El Paso County by Date
      Arranged chronologically and sequentially by entry number.
      - Entries 82018-84444, 1901 February 6-April 30 (Box 49, Folder 128)
      - Entries 84445-87119, 1901 May 1-July 31 (Box 49, Folder 129)
      - Entries 87120-88869, 1901 August 1-September 30 (Box 49, Folder 130)
      - Entries 88870-91125, 1901 October 1-November 30 (Box 50, Folder 131)
      - Entries 91126-94457, 1901 December 1-1902 February 28 (Box 50, Folder 132)
      - Entries 94458-96803, 1902 March 1-April 30 (Box 50, Folder 133)
      - Entries 96804-99766, 1902 May 1-July 31 (Box 51, Folder 134)
      - Entries 99767-102364, 1902 August 1-October 31 (Box 51, Folder 135)
    - Records of a Notary Public, (3 volumes)
      Records of estates, deeds, powers-of-attorney, and other business administered by Mary C. Trovinger (1880-1969), a notary public, as well as a stenographer and assistant secretary with the Security Abstract & Title Company.
      - Volume, 1907-1911 (Box 52, Folder 136)
      - Volume, 1924-1927 (Box 52, Folder 137)
      - Volume, 1933-1935 (Box 52, Folder 138)
  - Smith, Barton, McDonald & Co., 1892-1893
    Smith, Barton, McDonald & Co. was an abstract company active in the Cripple Creek region, Colorado, circa 1892-1893.
    - Abstracts, No. 1, 1892 May 4-1893 December 5 (Box 53 Oversize)
      Abstracts of legal instruments related to mines.
  - Teller and El Paso Abstract Company, 1887-1909
    This series is arranged under four headings: Indices; Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Type; Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date; and Sale Records for Delinquent Tax.
    Teller and El Paso Abstract Company was an abstract company active in the Cripple Creek, Colorado, circa 1901-1909.
    - Indices, circa 1891-1909
      - Name Index, circa 1891-1899 (Box 54 Oversize)
        Index to legal instruments on properties in towns and subdivisions in El Paso County and Teller County.
      - Index to Mining Claims, Teller County No. 1, circa 1895-1900 (Box 55 Oversize)
        Alphabetical list of mines that reference books and pages of claims.
      - Index to Mining Claims, Teller County, circa 1899-1909 (Box 56 Oversize)
      - Index to Lots and Blocks, Volume 2, Garden of Eden to Woodland Park, circa 1900-1906 (Box 57 Oversize)
      - Index to Land Claims, Teller County, circa 1900-1909 (Box 58 Oversize)
        Index to legal instruments on properties in Townships 11-18 and corresponding Ranges 68-71.
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Type, 1887-1896
      Arranged sequentially by book number
      Abstracts of legal instruments in El Paso County.
      Numeric designations for volumes refer to designations applied to the original record book in the county clerk's office, not to a sequence of volumes in the abstract company's office. Consequently a bound volume may abstract several volumes of legal instruments.
      - Book 45 (Patents), Book 96 (Trusts), Book 108 (Trusts and Trust Deeds), Book 159 (Trusts), and Book 218 (Various Legal Instruments), 1887 October 4-1895 December 3 (Box 59, Folder 139)
      - Book 87 (Trustee Deeds), Book 157 (Trustee Deeds), and Book 164 (Various Legal Instruments), 1891 March 20-1896 January 11 (Box 59, Folder 140)
      - Book 89 (Warranty Deeds) and Book 147 (Warranties), 1890 October 31-1893 January 27 (Box 59, Folder 141)
      - Book 110, Book 118, Book 120, Book 124, Book 132, Book 133, Book 170, and Book 180, 1889 January 25-1896 January 21 (Box 59, Folder 142)
        Abstracts for trusts and trust deed for property in El Paso County.
      - Book 125, Book 126, and Book 166, 1890 August 23-1896 February 25 (Box 60, Folder 143)
        Abstracts of warranties.
      - Book 139, Book 151, Book 161, Book 168, and Book 183, 1891 August 22-1896 January 10 (Box 60, Folder 144)
        Abstracts for releases.
      - Book 143 (Patents), 1892 March 27-1896 January 11 (Box 60, Folder 145)
      - Book 191 (Warranties and Warranty Deeds), 1895 January 9-September 14 (Box 60, Folder 146)
      - Book 192 and Book 193, 1894 September 14-1896 January 14 (Box 61, Folder 147)
        Abstracts of warranties and warranty deeds
      - Book 206 (Warranties), 1894 September 24-1896 January 7 (Box 61, Folder 148)
      - Blank Book, undated (Box 61, Folder 149)
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date, 1896-1906
      - Volume 0-1-2, Entries 1-2998, 1896 January 14-31 (Box 62, Folder 150)
      - Volume 3-4, Entries 2999-4999, 1896 January 31-February 12 (Box 62, Folder 151)
      - Volume 7-8, Entries 7001-8999, 1896 February 24-March 9 (Box 62, Folder 152)
      - Volume 17-18, Entries 17000-18999, 1896 May 2-June 4 (Box 62, Folder 153)
      - Volume 21-22, Entries 21002-22999, 1896 June 30-July 31 (Box 62, Folder 154)
      - Volume 23-24, Entries 23002-24999, 1896 July 31-September 2 (Box 62, Folder 155)
      - Volume 25-26, Entries 25000-26999, 1896 September 3-October 5 (Box 62, Folder 156)
      - Volume 27-28, Entries 27000-28999, 1896 October 5-November 14 (Box 63, Folder 157)
      - Volume 29-30, Entries 29000-30999, 1896 November 14-December 15 (Box 63, Folder 158)
      - Volume 31-32, Entries 31000-32999, 1896 December 15-1897 January 9 (Box 63, Folder 159)
      - Volume 33-34, Entries 33000-34999, 1897 January 9-February 11 (Box 63, Folder 160)
      - Volume 35-36, Entries 35000-36999, 1897 February 11-March 22 (Box 63, Folder 161)
      - Volume 37-38, Entries 37000-38999, 1897 March 22-April 29 (Box 63, Folder 162)
      - Volume 39-40, Entries 39000-40999, 1897 April 30-June 14 (Box 63, Folder 163)
      - Volume 41-42, Entries 41000-42999, 1897 June 14-July 29 (Box 64, Folder 164)
      - Volume 43-44, Entries 43000-44999, 1897 July 29-September 17 (Box 64, Folder 165)
      - Volume 45-46, Entries 45000-46999, 1897 September 19-November 5 (Box 64, Folder 166)
      - Volume 47-48, Entries 47000-48999, 1897 November 5- December 20 (Box 64, Folder 167)
      - Volume 51-52, Entries 50999-52998, 1898 January 20-February 28 (Box 64, Folder 168)
      - Volume 53-54, Entries 53000-54999, 1898 February 28-April 11 (Box 64, Folder 169)
      - Volume 30, Entries 30003-30999, 1901 May 29-1901 July 3 (Box 65, Folder 170)
      - Volume 35, Entries 34998-35999, 1901 December 9-1902 January 11 (Box 65, Folder 171)
      - Volume 37, Entries 36997-37999, 1902 February 18-March 27 (Box 65, Folder 172)
      - Volume 38, Entries 38000-39012, 1902 March 27-May 12 (Box 65, Folder 173)
      - Volume 39, Entries 39013-40005, 1902 May 12-July 1 (Box 65, Folder 174)
      - Volume 40, Entries 40006-40999, 1902 July 2-August 28 (Box 65, Folder 175)
      - Volume 41, Entries 41000-42000, 1902 August 28-October 23 (Box 65, Folder 176)
      - Volume 42, Entries 42001-43005, 1902 October 23-December 11 (Box 65, Folder 177)
      - Volume 43, Entries 43006-43999, 1902 December 12-1903 January 27 (Box 65, Folder 178)
      - Volume 44, Entries 44000-45005, 1903 January 27-April 4 (Box 65, Folder 179)
      - Volume 47, Entries 47002-47995, 1903 September 21-December 16 (Box 66, Folder 180)
      - Volume 48, Entries 47996-49004, 1903 December 17-1904 March 2 (Box 66, Folder 181)
      - Volume 49, Entries 49005-49999, 1904 March 2-May 23 (Box 66, Folder 182)
      - Volume 50, Entries 50000-51000, 1904 May 23-August 29 (Box 66, Folder 183)
      - Volume 51, Entries 51001-52007, 1904 August 29-December 7 (Box 66, Folder 184)
      - Volume 52, Entries 52008-53000, 1904 December 8-1905 February 11 (Box 66, Folder 185)
      - Volume 53, Entries 53001-54015, 1905 February 11-May 3 (Box 66, Folder 186)
      - Volume 54, Entries 54016-55009, 1905 May 4-July 20 (Box 66, Folder 187)
      - Volume 55, Entries 55010-56000, 1905 July 21-October 17 (Box 66, Folder 188)
      - Volume 57, Entries 57026-57999, 1906 January 6-March 21 (Box 67, Folder 189)
      - Volume 58, Entries 58000-59006, 1906 May 22-June 30 (Box 67, Folder 190)
    - Sale Records for Delinquent Tax, 1899-1902
      - Tax Sale Record, No. 2, Entries 1-4142, 1899 December 8-1900 December 7 (Box 68 Oversize)
        2 copies
        First portion documents the sale of property for delinquent taxes on December 8, 1899, with certificate entries 1-1420.
        Second portion documents the sale of property for delinquent taxes December 6-7, 1900, with certificate entries 1421-4142.
        - Duplicate copy., 1899 December 8-1900 December 7 (Box 69 Oversize)
      - Tax Sale Record, No. 3, Entries 4143-7261 and 1-2463, 1901 November 19-1902 November 18 (Box 70 Oversize)
        First portion documents the sale of property for delinquent taxes November 19-20, 1901, with certificate entries 4143-7261.
        Second portion documents the sale of property for delinquent taxes November 17-18, 1902, with certificate entries 1-2463.
  - Teller County Abstract Company, circa 1892-circa 1930
    The Teller County Abstract Company was an abstract company active in Cripple Creek, Colorado, 1899-circa 1930.
    - Lot Book for Cripple Creek and Subdivisions, circa 1892-circa 1930 (Box 71 Oversize)
      Volume records entry numbers for property lots in Cripple Creek and subdivisions.
- Records of Unidentified Abstract Companies, 1861-1940; Series II; 32.9; (107 boxes)
  This series is arranged into four subseries: Abstract Records of El Paso County; Abstract Records of Fremont County; Abstract Records of Teller County; and Discrete Records from Unidentified Abstract Companies.
  - Abstract Records of El Paso County, 1883-1899
    Records related to legal instruments applied to real estate in El Paso County. Many of these records were likely compiled by unidentified abstract companies.
    This subseries is arranged under four headings: Indices, Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Type, Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date, and Sale Records for Delinquent Taxes.
    - Indices, 1861-1896
      - Index to Wills, Powers of Attorney, and General Conveyances, 1861-1924 (Box 72 Oversize)
      - Index of Judgments and Liens, 1881-1895 (Box 73 Oversize)
        Index arranged alphabetically by plaintiff of judgments and liens.
      - Index to Judgments and Power of Attorney, 1894 November-1896 August (Box 74)
        Entries grouped alphabetically by the surname or corporate name of the defendant, or the principal granting the power.
      - Index to Wills, Powers of Attorney, and Incorporations, No. 9, 1896-1906 (Box 75 Oversize)
      - Index to Loans and Mortagages, 1898 December 1-1899 July 5 (Box 76 Oversize)
        Alphabetical index of lenders and debtors that refers to instrument entries and records dates and other notes.
      - Lot Book, circa 1900 (Box 77)
        Index of property lots for plats in El Paso County.
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Type, 1883-1896
      Arranged into three sets: Abstracts for Location Certificates of Lode Claims; Abstracts of Conveyances of Mining Deeds; and Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Type.
      Bound carbon copies of typescripts and handwritten entries that include abstracts of legal instruments related to real property and incorporation in El Paso County, Colorado, probably compiled by the Recorder of Deeds.
      - Abstracts for Location Certificates of Lode Claims, 1892-1895; (12 volumes)
        Entries within volumes are arranged chronologically.
        - Book 4, 1892 April 28-August 1 (Box 78, Folder 191)
        - Book 5, 1892 May 16-September 18 (Box 78, Folder 192)
        - Book 6, 1892 August 1-1893 April 27 (Box 78, Folder 193)
        - Book 7, 1892 September 19-1893 July 12 (Box 78, Folder 194)
        - Book 8, 1893 July 13-1894 February 16 (Box 78, Folder 195)
        - Book 9, 1894 February 16-1896 February 14 (Box 78, Folder 196)
        - Book 10, 1894 March 26-October 13 (Box 79, Folder 197)
        - Book 11, 1894 October 15-1895 June 26 (Box 79, Folder 198)
        - Book 12, 1894 March 26-1895 August 5 (Box 79, Folder 199)
        - Book 13, 1895 August 5-1896 January 15 (Box 79, Folder 200)
          Laid-in Location Certificate of Lode Claim by James Crook for a lode claim on the Little Maggie Lode, discovered on October 29, 1895, located on January 2, 1896, and filed on January 15, 1896.
        - Book 14, 1895 June 27-December 9 (Box 79, Folder 201)
        - Book 15 and Book 17, 1895 December 10-1896 January 14 (Box 79, Folder 202)
      - Abstracts of Conveyances of Mining Deeds, 1893-1895
        Most entries arranged chronologically within volumes by their date of record.
        - Book 163 and Book 169, 1893 June 2-1894 March 24 (Box 80, Folder 203)
        - Book 202 and Book 210, 1894 August 13-1895 May 18 (Box 80, Folder 204)
        - Book 220 and Book 221, 1895 May 18-1895 November 30 (Box 80, Folder 205)
        - Book 222 and Book 223, 1895 November 30-1896 January 14 (Box 80, Folder 206)
      - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Type
        Arranged with oversize volumes followed sequentially by volumes with book numbers.
        Numbers applied to books likely correspond to volumes in the offices of the Teller County Clerk & Recorder.
        Most entries are arranged chronologically within volumes by their date of record, except for Book A, which is arranged by certificate number.
        Dates overlap between the volumes.
        - Title Abstracts Walton's Abstract Lots, No. 4, 1883 December 8-1888 March 21 (Box 81 Oversize)
          Abstracts recorded using a system developed by William Edward Walton (born 1842). Volume documents the plats of Palmer Lake, the Cascade Addition to Palmer Lake, and Glen Park.
          Entries arrnaged by block and lot number
        - Parties Booklet, No. 125, 1890 August 26-1896 January 9 (Box 82)
          Bound carbon copies of manuscript and typescript abstracts of legal instruments, probably warranties.
        - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Type, 1891 October 24-1916 December 29 (Box 83 Oversize)
          Pages 1-35 document powers of attorney, October 24, 1891, to December 7, 1893.
          Pages 151-268 document certificates of incorporation, March 13, 1891, to December 14, 1893.
          Pages 269-285 have chiefly affixed abstracts of certificates of incorporation and amended certificates of incorporation, April 18, 1892, to December 29, 1916. Some of these instruments were filed in other counties.
        - Book 79 (Variety of Legal Instruments), 1886 November 30-1892 May 26 (Box 84, Folder 207)
        - Book 117 (Quit Claim Deeds), 1890 May 20-1892 October 22 (Box 84, Folder 208)
        - Book 128 (Warranty Deeds), 1891 July 17-1892 February 24 (Box 84, Folder 209)
        - Book 129 (Warranty Deeds), 1892 February 25 -1892 July 30 (Box 85, Folder 210)
          Many laid-in loose abstracts and notes throughout the volume.
        - Book 142 (Mining Deeds), Book 144 (Warranty Deeds), and Book 145 (Mining Deeds), 1891 December 1-1892 July 13 (Box 85, Folder 211)
        - Book 151 (Deeds of Title) and Book 152 (Quit Claim Deeds), 1892 June 7-1894 May 21 (Box 85, Folder 212)
        - Book 153 (Mining Deeds), 1892 July 22-1893 January 3 (Box 85, Folder 213)
        - Book 171 (Mining Deeds), 1894 March 24-1894 August 11 (Box 85, Folder 214)
        - Book 174 (Quit Claim Deeds) and Book 175, 1894 May 23- December 31 (Box 86, Folder 215)
          Book 174 dates from June 6 to December 31, 1894.
          Book 175 dates from May 23 to October 26, 1894.
        - Book 204, 1894 December 29-1895 June 3 (Box 86, Folder 216)
        - Book 217 (Quit Claim Deeds), Book 176 (Decrees, Judgments, Levies, Liens, Lis Pendens, and Notices), Book 191 (Warranty Deeds), and Book 192 (Warranty Deeds), 1894 December 4-1896 January 14 (Box 86, Folder 217)
          Book 217 dates from October 28, 1895, to January 14, 1896.
          Book 176 dates from December 4, 1894, to January 14, 1896.
          Book 191 dates from January 9 to June 26, 1895.
          Book 192 dates from September 14 to December 28, 1895.
          Laid-in manuscript transcript of a warranty deed from S. G. Porter to the Florence & Cripple Creek Railroad Company for property in Victor, Colorado.
        - Book 218, 1895 October 16-1896 January 7 (Box 86, Folder 218)
        - Book A (Certificates of Incorporation and Stock Payments), Book 228, and Book 214, 1894 October-1896 January 14 (Box 86, Folder 219)
          Book A dates from October 1894 to December 1895.
          Book 228 dates from December 16, 1895, to January 14, 1896.
          Book 214 dates from June 3 to July 22, 1895.
    - Abstracts of Legal Instruments by Date, 1895-1899
      Sets of volumes that compile abstracts of legal instruments arranged by date.
      Alphanumeric designations for volumes and entry numbers refer to designations applied to the original record book in the county clerk's office, not to a sequence of volumes in the abstract company's office. Consequently a bound volume may abstract several volumes of legal instruments.
      Arranged into three sets: First Set, 1893-1896; Second Set, 1895-1899; and Third Set, 1896-1899
      - First Set, 1893-1896
        Handwritten abstracts of legal instruments.
        - Pages 771-1100, 1893 December 13-28 (Box 87, Folder 220)
          Includes tipped in abstracts and legal instruments in the front of the volume, January 11, 1892, to February 23, 1895
        - Pages 1111-1400, 1893 December 28-1894 January 13 (Box 87, Folder 221)
        - Pages 1401-1649, 1894 January 13-February 9 (Box 87, Folder 222)
        - Pages 1650-1983, 1894 February 9-March 19 (Box 88, Folder 223)
        - Pages 1984-2317, 1894 March 19-April 27 (Box 88, Folder 224)
        - Pages 2317-2651, 1894 April 27-June 28 (Box 88, Folder 225)
        - Pages 2880-3104, 1894 July 28-August 31 (Box 89, Folder 226)
        - Pages 3105-3323, 1894 September 1-October 19 (Box 89, Folder 227)
        - Pages 3324-3589, 1894 October 20-December 1 (Box 89, Folder 228)
        - Pages 3590-3850, 1875 June 2- 1894 December 31 (Box 89, Folder 229)
          Pages 3590-3736 covers December 1-31, 1894.
          Pages 3737-3850 covers June 2, 1875, to June 30, 1888.
        - Pages 3851-4081, 1867 July 31-1889 December 31 (Box 90, Folder 230)
          Pages 3851-3956 covers June 30, 1888, to December 31, 1889.
          Pages 3957-3967 arranged in descending chronology and covers August 27, 1884, to May 2, 1885.
          Pages 3968-4014 covers July 31, 1867, to August 26, 1884.
          Pages 4001-4015 transposed in the volume
        - Pages 4082-4274, 1890 January 1-1892 June 27 (Box 90, Folder 231)
        - Pages 4275-4543, 1892 June 27-1896 April 22 (Box 90, Folder 232)
      - Second Set, 1895-1899
        - Volume 4, Pages 1-250, 1895 January 2-1895 February 11 (Box 91, Folder 233)
          Laid-in abstracts of legal instruments, February 13, 1890; January 30, 1891; and May 9, 1891.
        - Volume 4, Pages 251-500, 1895 February 11-April 17 (Box 91, Folder 234)
        - Volume 4, Pages 501-750, 1895 April 17-June 10 (Box 91, Folder 235)
        - Volume 4, Pages 751-1000, 1895 June 10-August 1 (Box 92, Folder 236)
        - Volume 5, Pages 1-250, 1895 August 1-September 18 (Box 92, Folder 237)
        - Volume 5, Pages 250-500, 1895 September 18-November 1 (Box 92, Folder 238)
        - Volume 5, Pages 751-100, 1895 November 27-1895 December 16 (Box 93, Folder 239)
        - Volume 6, Pages 1-285, 1895 December 16-30 (Box 93, Folder 240)
        - Volume 6, Pages 286-573, 1895 December 30-1896 January 14 (Box 93, Folder 241)
        - Volume 6, Pages 574-1000, Entries 1-2643, 1896 January 14-30 (Box 94, Folder 242)
          Includes a tipped in Letters of Administration, February 1, 1894, that appoints Anna A. Faulkner as the administratrix for the estate of Simon P. Faulkner (died January 23, 1894)
        - Volume 7, Pages 1-250, Entries 2644-3708, 1896 January 30-February 5 (Box 94, Folder 243)
        - Volume 7, Pages 251-500, Entries 3725-4813, 1896 February 5-11 (Box 94, Folder 244)
        - Volume 7, Pages 501-750, Entries 4814-5979, 1896 February 11-18 (Box 95, Folder 245)
        - Volume 7, Pages 751-1000, Entries 5980-7222, 1896 February 18-25 (Box 95, Folder 246)
        - Volume 8, Pages 1-500, Entries 7223-9634, 1896 February 25-13 (Box 95, Folder 247)
        - Volume 8, Pages 501-1000, Entries 9635-11995, 1896 March 13-28 (Box 96, Folder 248)